gotvape.net 2011-10-17

# Privacy Policy

## GotVape.com Privacy Policy

We understand that you have **confidential information** that you want to protect and maintain as confidential. We want you to know that Got Vape? is committed to safeguarding your privacy online and that we strive to make our Web site as safe and secure as reasonably possible.

In order to address our users most frequently asked questions we've organized our privacy policy statement in a Q&A format. If you have any questions after reading this policy, please let us know. Send us an email at [customer.serv...@GotVape.com](mailto:%20customer.service@gotvape.com).

## What information does Got Vape? collect from me?

During registration we ask for your name, company name, address, zip/postal code, email address, phone, age. In addition to the information we obtain at registration, we may ask you for information at other times, such as when you make a purchase or register for a service on www.gotvape.com Web site, when you submit a listing for a Web site, or when you report a problem with one of our services or the site(s) of our strategic alliance companies.

If you contact Got Vape? we may keep a record of that correspondence or communication. Information on how you communicated with us may also be recorded and can include your Internet address, the language you selected for viewing order forms or other documents, your browser type, the currency in which you viewed prices if such feature is available, your use of a secure or insecure Web page, the return email address shown in any email message from you, the return address on any envelope or facsimile number on any facsimile, or the telephone number from which you called.

Got Vape? also may occasionally ask you to provide information to participate in certain voluntary promotions, surveys, or contests (see the Sponsors/Contests/Surveys section below). Finally, Got Vape? collects information about its Members in general, which does not necessarily identify the Member, by using our server log files and some of the methods described in the "cookies" section below.

## Why does Got Vape? gather this information, and how is it used?

  * When you order a product or service we use your name, email address, delivery address, and credit card number and expiration date (or financial information) as part of a credit check. This information allows us to process the order and deliver the product or service. 
  * We ask for your telephone number to enable us to contact you if there is a problem with your order or the delivery of a product or service. In the event you have asked for the delivery of tangible goods, we may need to share the telephone number with the carrier delivering the goods
  * When you order a product or service from a company linked to the www.gotvape.com Web site, it may be necessary for Got Vape? to share certain limited information, such as your IP address, with such company in order to process and complete your purchase or other transaction. In such cases, Got Vape? shares the minimum information necessary to complete the transaction and only shares such information when you make a purchase or engage in a transaction - not when you simply visit and leave the other site.
  * If you choose to enter a contest or other promotion, we ask for your name, address, email address, and other information in order to notify winners. As noted in the rules of the contest or promotion, we may publish certain information about the winners.
  * In addition to using your information to deliver services requested by you, Got Vape? may use the information to notify you about important service issues, functionality changes, and other customer support issues. If you choose, Got Vape? will also notify you about special offers and services from Got Vape? that we believe you will find valuable.
  * We also use the information you provide us to enhance the operation of the www.gotvape.com Web site and to provide you a customized experience when you navigate through our site.
  * Finally, we analyze our users' demographics, interests, and behavior based on the information provided to us through the www.gotvape.com Web site. Our research and analysis is done on an aggregate basis and is not intended to identify individual Members. 

## What about third party sites linked to the www.gotvape.com Web site or strategic alliance companies?

Certain products and services offered through the www.gotvape.com Web site are made available by other companies with which Got Vape? has a strategic alliance. To obtain some of these products and services you may be on the other company's Web site or a site they share with Got Vape?. When ordering, registering for, or purchasing products or services from these other companies, you will be entering into an agreement with that company, not with Got Vape?. In these cases, this privacy policy does not apply; instead, the privacy policy of the company actually providing the goods or services will apply. We urge you to read and understand those policies before entering into agreements with such companies. We are committed to working with companies that share our privacy concerns. Got Vape?, however, can't control or take responsibility for the way these companies collect or use information.

Also, when you access the Web site of another company, an advertiser, or Web site linked from the www.gotvape.com Web site, those companies or sites may use cookies or other means to collect information about you. Again, the www.gotvape.com privacy policy does not apply to these instances; instead, the privacy policy of the site you visit will apply.

Third party vendors, including Google, show GotVape.com ads on sites on the internet. Third Party vendors, including Google, Also use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to GotVape.com.

Users may opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting the Google Advertising opt-out page. (Alternatively you can opt out of a third party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt out page.)

If you have questions about the privacy policies of strategic alliance companies or the privacy policies of other sites, we encourage you to contact them directly.
